http://www.eastwestintl.com/privacypolicy.html

Login
Shopping Cart (0)
Your Cart is Empty
Toll Free:877-658-8658
Contact No:713-789-6611
220 Volt Appliances (Overseas use only)Air ConditionersBuilt in OvensCook TopsCooking RangesDehumidifiersDishwashersElectric Commercial FryersElectric Commercial GriddlesElectric Convection OvensExhaust FanFreezersGarbage DisposalsIce MakersMicrowave OvensPharmaceutical and Vaccination RefrigeratorRange HoodsRefrigeratorsTrash CompactorsWarming DrawerWashers And DryersWater CoolersWater Heaters Tankless Water HeatersWater Purifiers Distillers and FiltersWine Coolers and Beverage CentersMultisystem ElectronicsCamcordersConverters MultisystemDVD Players Blu Ray Players MultizoneStereo And Home Theatre SystemsTVS LED LCD and Plasma And MultisystemVideo ProjectorsOffice ProductsCalculatorsCash RegisterCopiersCordless TelephonesDocument BindersElectric StaplersFax MachinesLaminatorsMonitorsPaper ShreddersPencil SharpenersPrinters Scanners And Multifunction MachinesProjection ScreensProjectorsScannersType WritersPower ToolsAngle GrindersBand SawsBench GrindersBlowersChain SawsChop Saws Cut Off SawsCircular SawsCompressorsConcrete GrinderCordless ToolsDie GrindersDrill PressesDrills DriversGarden ToolsGlue GunsHeat GunsImpact WrenchsJig SawsLathe MachinesMarble CutterMetal SawsMiter SawsNailersNibblersPlanersPlate JoinerPower Mixers and Concrete MixersPressure WashersRotary ToolRoutersSander PolishersSandersSawzalls Sabre Saws Raciprocation SawsScrewdriversShearsSoldering Irons Soldering GunsSpray GunStraight GrindersTable SawsTrimmersCountertop Appliances110Volt 60Hz Kitchen AppliancesBlendersBread MakersCan OpenersChoppersCoffee GrindersCoffee Makers And PercolatorsCrock Pot Slow CookersDeep FryersElectric KnifesFood Processors Kitchen CentersFood Saver Vacuum Bag SealerFood SteamersGrills Griddles Hot Plates SkilletsHand BlendersHand MixersHot DispenserIce Cream MakersJuicersKettlesMeat Grinders And Meat SlicersPopcorn MakersRice CookersSandwich MakersStand Mixer (Commercial)Stand MixersThermopotsToaster OvensToastersTortilla MakerWaffle Pancake MakersYogurt MakersOther 220 Volt ProductsAir PurifiersBattery ChargersChristmas LightsClock Radios Alarm ClockDesk LampElectric Insect Killers Roach KillerEmergency Flood Exit Lights Motion DetectorExcercise EquipmentsFansFireplaceGarment SteamerGeneratorsHair And Beauty CareHealth Care ProductsHeaters And RadiatorsHumidifiers And VaporizersIroning BoardIrons And Steam PressLight Bulbs Bulb HoldersNight LightsSewing MachinesSmoke DetectorsVacuum Cleaners And Shampoo PolishersTransformers And ConvertersLine Regulators and ConditionersPlug Adapters Extension Cords and Telephone JacksStep Up and Step Down TransformersSurge ProtectorsTransformers (U.S.A to Japan) OR (Japan to U.S.A)Travel Converters and Low Wattage TransformersUPS System for ComputersVoltage RegulatorsWorld TV Broadcast System Chart
Home
Shop By Category
»220 Volt Appliances (Overseas use only)»Multisystem Electronics»Office Products»Power Tools»Countertop Appliances»Other 220 Volt Products»Transformers And Converters»World TV Broadcast System Chart
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (www.eastwestintl.com) this privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the followingWhat personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website and how it is used and with whom it may be shareWhat choices are available to you regarding the use of your dataThe security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us such as; name, address, phone and billing information via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order, Unless you ask us not to. We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access and Control over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email info@eastwestintl.com
SIGN UP FOR OUR NEWSLETTER !
Address:
Prices and specifications are subject to change. Pictures may vary. We are not responsible
for typographical errors.
×
Login to your account
